《訴訟雙雄》前情提要
我想讓自己合法化
I want to go legit.
你不能
You can't.
那我找羅拉·詹森黑進資格考名單
Then I get Lola Jensen to hack into the bar
把我名字加進去  就像她黑哈佛一樣
and just put me in there, just like she did with Harvard.
不想被人抓到辮子
Rule number one of not getting caught,
就是別輕舉妄動
you don't move the goddamn body.
哈維  我無路可走了
Harvey, I'm stuck.
我不能這樣過一輩子
I can't live my whole life like this.
我們是投資銀行家
We're investment bankers.
我們的工作比你們的厲害多了
Our job blows yours out of the water.
承認吧  你想讓我接受那份工作
Just admit it. You want me to take the job,
但你不敢說
but you're too afraid to say it.
我希望你接受那份工作
I want you to take the job.
你和你的手下與哈羅德·甘德森合謀
You and your associate conspired with Harold Gunderson
對你們自己的客戶發起了訴訟
to file a lawsuit against your own client.
那就是賄賂
That is a bribe.
柯靈知道了你與哈羅德·甘德森
Quelling knows about your bullshit lawsuit
那個狗屁官司了
with Harold Gunderson.
打電話給羅拉·詹森
You need to call Lola Jensen.
你自己也說過  黑進資格考名單
You said it yourself. Hacking into the bar
比我現在犯的罪還重一倍
is twice the crime I've been committing.
我告訴你  柯靈發現你了
I am telling you Quelling is on the trail.
就算你辭職也無濟于事
And you quitting isn't gonna change that.
你讓邁克走了
You're letting Mike walk out the door
甚至沒有試圖阻攔他
without trying to stop him.
每次我問你什么事
Any time I ask you about anything,
你都只會告訴我你不能說
all you say is, "I can't talk about it."
邁克就要走了  哈維
Look, Mike is gone, Harvey.
這樣威脅也沒了
The jeopardy's gone too.
現在你卻想回過頭告訴
And now you want to turn around and tell someone
一個一直找理由生你氣的人
who keeps finding a reason to be pissed at you,
不是第三次了  也不是第五次
and it's not the third time, and it's not the fifth time,
當然也不是最后一次
and it's not the last time.
你收了我方客戶競爭對手的錢
You took money from our client's competitors
捏造了案子
to trump up your bullshit suit.
懲罰是剝奪律師資格
The penalty is being disbarred.
我生來就是律師
Being a lawyer is what I am.
若你奪走...
If you take that away...
決定權在你
It's up to you.
我會撤銷訴訟
I'll drop the suit.
我正式成為紐約律師協會的一員了
I'm officially a member of the New York bar.
你去找羅拉了
You went to Lola?
我想留下來
I want to stay.
我很想拿香檳來
I'd bring in champagne,
但經歷了那么多
but after all we've been through,
我們還是喝威士忌更合適
I think scotch seems more appropriate.
是嗎
Does it?
哈維  我們談過了
Harvey, we've had this conversation once.
如果你想要一個不把心里話說出來的人
If you want someone who doesn't speak their mind,
那你得另請高明了
I'm not that person.
我知道
I know.
而且邁克留下也不會改變我的想法
And Mike staying doesn't change my opinion.
告訴斯科特他的事是錯誤的
Telling Scottie about him is a mistake.
我知道
I know.
那你怎么那么沉默
Then why are you being so quiet?
一個一直找理由生你氣的人
Someone who keeps finding a way to be pissed at me,
不是第三次了  也不是第五次
and it's not the third time or the fifth time
也不是最后一次
or the last time.
-我沒想這么說的  -可你說了
- I wasn't gonna say that. - Yeah, well, you did.
是你逼我的
Because you forced it out of me.
唐娜  你希不希望我跟斯考特好下去
Donna, do you want me and Scottie to succeed or not?
我希望你幸福
I want you to be happy.
-這是在逃避  -不是的
- That's an evasive answer. - No, it isn't.
但我不能定義什么是你的幸福
Just isn't up to me to decide what that means.
我們要不要喝酒慶祝邁克留下了
Now are we gonna drink to Mike staying or what?
給我
Give me that.
不要那杯
Not that one.
大的那杯
The bigger one.
真的
Seriously?
你回來太好了
I'm so glad you're home.
我做了晚飯  因為我想慶祝
I made dinner because I want to celebrate.
我不會接受那份工作
I'm not taking the job.
什么
What?
我去見哈維了
I went to see Harvey, and, um...
我告訴他我要留下了
I told him that I'm staying.
那這事讓你寢食難安就不管了嗎
What about the fact that it was eating you up?
瑞秋  我知道你不想要這樣
Look, Rachel, I know this isn't what you wanted.
我不想
What I wanted?
我根本不想發表意見
I didn't wanna give you my opinion at all,
但你非逼我說出來
but you forced it out of me,
然后你告訴我你會接受這份工作
and then you told me that you were gonna take the job.
瑞秋  聽我說...
Okay, Rachel--
不要  現在你又來跟我說
No, and now you come in here,
你要繼續做個騙子
and you tell me you're gonna stay a fraud.
-是律師  -是騙子
- A lawyer. - A fraud.
你不是愿意接受我真實的樣子嗎
What happened to accepting me for who I am?
你不是要接受那份工作嗎
What happened to you taking the job?
那是條出路
It was a way out.
你說你擔心如果你說出了你的看法
You said you were afraid if you told me your opinion,
我會為此責備你
I'd hold it against you,
但現在我沒有按照你說的做
but now that I'm not doing what you told me to,
你要為此責備我
you're holding it against me.
是的
I am.
這不公平
Yeah, that's not fair.
我要知道從你說
I wanna know what changed
你打算接受那份工作到現在發生了什么
from when you told me you were gonna take the job to now.
我去見柯靈了
I went to see Quelling.
曾有人給他開出了很不錯的條件
He once had an offer on the table
足以改變他的生活
that would change his life,
他卻拒絕了
and he turned it down
因為他想為他的客戶努力爭取
because he wanted to do what was right for his clients.
這害他失去一切
Cost him everything.
他還唯一擁有的
The only thing it didn't cost him
就是能繼續做律師
was his ability to practice law.
我不想奪走那一點
And I didn't want to take it away from him
我也不想奪走我自己做律師的機會
just like I don't wanna take it away from me.
-邁克  -你說留下會讓我寢食難安
- Mike - You said that staying is eating me up,
但想到要離開  我更痛苦
but the thought of going is eating me up more.
我還沒準備好  瑞秋
I'm just--I'm not ready to leave, Rachel.
謝謝
Thanks.
邁克·羅斯
Michael Ross.
我是
Yes?
我們想問你幾個問題
We'd like to ask you a few questions.
你們是誰
Who's "We"?
聯邦檢察官辦公室
The U.S. Attorney's office.
有什么事
What can I help you with?
我們希望能私下談談
We'd prefer to have this conversation in private.
-希望  -堅持
- Prefer? - Insist.
斯科特
Scottie.
我知道我們吵了一架
I know we got in a fight,
但10點前喝酒就能解決問題了嗎
but drinking before 10:00 a.m., is that really the answer?
《廣告狂人》里就這樣
It is on Mad Men.
而且那家伙拽什么啊
Who's that guy think he is anyway?
邁克不走了
Mike's staying.
你一定很高興
You must be happy.
是啊
I am.
斯科特  我會對你更加坦誠
Scottie, I'm gonna do better about being open with you.
好
Good.
我們沒事了吧
Are we good?
沒事了
We're good.
我們今晚出去玩玩吧
Then let's go out tonight and have some fun.
好啊
I'm in.
斯科特
Scottie.
怎么
Yeah?
去個沒去過的地方吧
Let's go somewhere new.
唐娜  別教訓我
Donna, I don't wanna hear it.
我沒跟她說邁克的事
I didn't tell her about Mike.
哈維  斯特芬妮·利斯頓剛剛給我打了電話
Harvey, Stephanie Liston just called me.
你在聯邦檢察官辦公室的那個朋友
Your friend from the U.S. Attorney's office?
她說邁克剛剛被帶去問話
She said they just brought Mike in for questioning.
羅斯先生  我是埃里克·伍德爾
Mr. Ross, Eric Woodall.
我是聯邦檢察官...
I'm the U.S. Attorney--
負責紐約南部地區
For the southern district of New York.
我知道你是哪位
Yeah, I know who you are.
那你就知道自己有大麻煩了
Then you know you're in a shitload of trouble.
你是自己坦白還是我說
You wanna come clean, or should I lay it out for you?
我不知道你在說什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你跟哈羅德·甘德森密謀
you conspired with Harold Gunderson
欺騙了美國政府
to defraud the United States government
賄賂了艾娃·海辛頓一案中對她不利的證人
by paying off witnesses against Ava Hessington.
什么
What?
你似乎很吃驚
You sound surprised.
是啊  因為這純屬胡扯
I am because it's bullshit.
不是胡扯
It's not bullshit.
你要蹲很久的監獄了  朋友
You're facing some major prison time, my friend.
-我不是你的朋友  -可以做朋友啊
- I'm not your friend. - You can be.
不必了
Pass.
我和解了一樁訴訟  我沒做什么違法的事
I settled a lawsuit, okay? I didn't do anything wrong.
我也這么想的
Hey, I don't think you did.
至少不是你自己做的
Well, not on your own anyway.
你有什么要問的嗎
Is there a question?
得了  你是個機靈的年輕人
Come on, you're a bright young man.
你看得出我想要什么
You see where I'm going.
我不要交易員
I don't want the dealer.
我要真正拿錢的
I want the supplier.
哈維·斯佩克特
Harvey Specter.
你供出他  我馬上跟你做交易
Roll over on him, I'll cut a deal right now.
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
翻譯：草草   Reginamoon   某豚   王大可
翻譯：七個柚子醬   親愛的小飯     校對：王小麥
時間軸：憑陵新月   SumenQ   小式     精軸：小式
后期：冰冰愛尖尖       總監：swears
本字幕由人人影視字幕組翻譯
禁止用作任何商業盈利行為
訴 訟 雙 雄
第三季   第十六集
本季終
哈維·斯佩克特  我是邁克·羅斯的律師
Harvey Specter. I represent Mike Ross.
你不能過去  先生
Sir, you can't go back there. Sir!
你好啊
Well, hey there.
你要起訴他嗎
Are you charging him?
-暫時不  -那他跟我走
- Not at the moment. - Then he's coming with me.
你無權帶他來
And you had no right to bring him in.
我就有這個權利
I had every right to bring him in,
但那無所謂  他是自愿來的
but it doesn't matter 'cause he came in voluntarily.
那他這就要走了
And he's leaving immediately.
我們只是在友好地聊聊
We were just having a friendly conversation
艾娃·海辛頓一案中那些
about the witnesses who suddenly fell out
突然消失的證人
of the Ava Hessington case.
看來你的手下跟布萊頓-古爾德的
Seems your associate was a little chummy
一個律師是好朋友
with the associate at Bratton Gould.
好像是叫哈維·甘德森吧
Harvey Gunderson, I think, is his name.
是哈羅德·甘德森
Harold Gunderson.
是啊
You're right.
你才是哈維
You're Harvey.
我上庭之前可得把名字記清楚了
I gotta keep this all straight in my head before I make my case.
等我把哈羅德找來
Because once we bring Harold in,
他就會指證邁克
he'll point the finger at Mike,
邁克就只能
who will then have no choice
指證你了  哈維
but to bring it right home to you, Harvey.
我保證我再不會忘記你的名字了
I promise I won't forget your name again.
給我開門
Open that door.
跟你聊得很開心  邁克
Good talking to you, Mike.
希望以后有很多機會再談
Hope it's the first of many.
杰西卡  我有可怕的事要告訴你
Jessica, I have some dire news.
我剛剛路過會議室
I was just walking by the conference room,
然后我看見麥克斯·波拉德一個人在里面坐著
and I saw Max Pollard sitting there all by himself.
哈維沒出現嗎
Harvey was a no-show?
別擔心  我會搞定一切的
Don't worry, I took care of everything,
但是這可不像哈維會做的事
but it's not like Harvey to miss a meeting.
謝謝你  路易  我會調查這件事的
Thank you, Louis. I'll look into it.
你瞧  事情就是這樣了
You see, that's just it.
我覺得他可能有點不對勁
I think something might be wrong with him.
你是說他是個間諜嗎
You mean like he's a spy?
不是  杰西卡  聽著
No, Jessica, listen.
自從我心臟病發以來
Ever since my heart attack,
我一直在擔心其他人的健康
I've been worrying about other people's health.
我本來可以問唐娜的  但是我不想
And I'd ask Donna, but I don't wanna burden her
讓她擔心哈維終有一死
with the knowledge of his mortality.
你覺得唐娜不知道哈維是凡人也會死嗎
You don't think Donna knows Harvey can die?
杰西卡  我知道
Look, Jessica, I know
哈維看起來精瘦而且挺健康的
Harvey appears to be lean and relatively fit,
但就算是最帥的人也可能得冠心病
but coronary disease can strike even the most handsome.
路易  聽我說
Louis, listen to me.
哈維沒事  他也沒得過心臟病
Harvey isn't sick. He didn't have a heart attack.
而就算他錯過了那次會議
And if he missed that meeting,
我肯定他有個好理由
I'm sure there's a reasonable explanation.
我確信你是對的
I'm sure you're right.
我要去查查我的血壓了
I'm gonna go check my blood pressure.
好主意
Oh, good idea.
哈維死哪去了
Where the hell is Harvey?
他有錯過什么事嗎
Is he supposed to be somewhere he's not?
唐娜  別和我玩這套
Donna, no games.
他放了個老客戶的鴿子
He missed a meeting with a longtime client,
所以要么是你工作出錯了  而你從沒出過錯
so either you screwed up, which you never do,
要么就是有什么緊急情況我卻不知道
or there's an emergency I'm not being told about.
兩者兼有
Both.
意思是
Meaning?
我忘了取消那個會議
I forgot to cancel that meeting
因為有個緊急情況
because there's an emergency.
怎么回事
What is it?
邁克·羅斯今天早上被叫去問話了
Mike Ross got called in for questioning this morning.
真是對不起  哈維
Sorry about this, Harvey.
有可能會更糟的
Could have been worse.
你覺得他們有抓到什么把柄嗎
You thought they had me for being a fraud?
我不覺得他們是因為
Well, I didn't think they had you
你逾期未還書而抓你
for overdue library books.
你為什么會跟他們走
Why'd you go with them in the first place?
你奶奶沒教過你
Didn't your grandmother ever teach you
別上陌生人的車嗎
not to get into cars with strangers?
我試圖表現的配合一點
I was being cooperative.
別再做這種事了
Well, don't do that again.
該死的柯靈
Goddamn Quelling.
他不僅向律師協會舉報了我們
He didn't just hand us to the bar.
還去找了司法部
He went to the justice department.
簡直不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我看著他的雙眼  他向我保證過的
I looked him in the eye. He gave me his word.
滾他大爺的  我要去律師協會舉報他
Screw that guy. I'm turning him into the bar.
現在他不是我們的問題
Right now he's not our problem.
哈羅德才是
Harold is.
不  我會去和他談談的
No, I'm gonna talk to him.
想都別想
Not a chance.
哈維  他們還沒把他牽扯進來
Harvey, they haven't brought him in yet.
我只需要花上五分鐘告訴他
All I need is five minutes to tell him--
要堅持你編的故事
-- to stick to your story?
那正是他們還沒把他牽扯進來的原因
That's exactly why they haven't brought him in yet.
你一去找哈羅德談
You talk to Harold,
他們就會發現  我們就完了
they'll be watching, we'll be done.
假如我們不趕在這個叫伍德爾的人叫他去談話之前
If we don't talk to him before this Woodall guy
和他談談  我們就麻煩大了
gets him in the room, we're in deep shit.
那我們得在不和他直接接觸的情況下和他談談
Then we need to talk to him without talking to him.
艾莉森·霍特
Allison Holt.
哈維·斯佩克特
Harvey Specter.
我一點也不驚訝會見到你
Can't say I'm surprised to see you.
我猜這意味著你已經和聯邦檢察官談過了
So I assume that means you've spoken to the U.S. Attorney.
的確
I have.
那我建議我們確認一下
Then I suggest we make sure
我倆依然有所共識
we're on the same page.
和你不一樣  我可不會
Unlike you, I don't automatically
保護某個可能會威脅到我律所的人
protect someone who may have jeopardized my firm.
伍德爾去找你時你到底說了什么
What exactly did you say when Woodall came to you?
他沒來找我  是我去找他的
He didn't come to me. I went to him.
什么
What?
一個叫詹姆斯·柯靈的人來找過我
A man named James Quelling came at me,
詢問那個哈羅德·甘德森以及邁克·羅斯
Questioning the settlement between Harold Gunderson,
還有你的謀殺案證人達成的和解
Mike Ross, and your murder witnesses.
所以你就直接去找了聯邦檢察官
So you go straight to the U.S. Attorney?
我的誠信受到了質疑
My integrity was questioned.
首先要做的可不是去找
First step isn't to go to the person
我被指控與其勾結的人  來掩蓋事實
I'm accused of colluding with to cover it up.
就回答我一個問題
Answer me one thing--
哈羅德·甘德森知道發生了什么事嗎
Does Harold Gunderson know what's going on?
我不知道他知道些什么
I don't know what he knows,
而且  坦白地說  我不在乎
and, frankly, I don't care.
我一小時前炒了哈羅德·甘德森
I fired Harold Gunderson an hour ago.
我能和你談一小會兒嗎
Can I talk to you for a second?
當然
Of course.
我剛剛被帶去市中心了
I just got taken downtown.
什么
What?
聯邦檢察官辦公室把我帶去問話
The U.S. Attorney's office brought me in for questioning.
我以為是因為我自己的事  但其實不是
I thought it was about me, but it wasn't.
謝天謝地
Thank god.
不  瑞秋  情況還是很糟糕
No, Rachel, it's still bad.
他們在調查艾娃的審判前
They're looking into the settlement
我和哈羅德的和解協議
that I made with Harold before Ava's trial.
那個交易可不完全是合法的
That deal wasn't exactly legitimate.
而他們希望我告發哈維
And they want me to turn on Harvey.
人人影視
YYeTs.com
我就知道你應接受那份工作的
I knew you should have taken that job.
這個和那個沒關系
This has nothing to do with that.
沒有嗎
Doesn't it?
假如你不在這兒工作
If you weren't working here,
他們就不能利用你和哈維的關系
they wouldn't be able to use your relationship
來做籌碼了
with Harvey as leverage.
你覺得我不在這里工作的話
You think I would turn my back on him
就會背棄他嗎
even if I wasn't working here?
我覺得你永遠不會背棄哈維
I don't think you'd ever turn your back on Harvey.
而那正是問題所在
That's the problem.
-這是什么意思  -哈維想讓你留下
- What does that mean? - Harvey wanted you to stay.
我想要你離開  你選擇了留下
I wanted you to leave. You chose to stay.
所以你的優先考慮對象  在我看來已經很清楚了
So your priorities, they seem pretty clear to me.
-瑞秋  拜托  -等等
- Rachel, come on. - Hey, wait a minute.
假如他們要起訴你
If they charge you with something,
他們就要查看你的記錄
they're gonna go through your records,
然后他們就會發現
and they are going to realize
你不是律師協會的一員
that you're not a member of the bar.
不  他們不會發現的
No, they won't.
你在說什么呢
What are you talking about?
我讓羅拉·詹森黑進了律師協會名單
I had Lola Jensen hack into the bar
把我加進記錄里了
and put me in their records.
你本來打算什么時候告訴我這件事呢
And when were you going to tell me?
我昨晚本來想告訴你一切的
I was going to tell you everything last night,
但你當時看起來不太有心情
but you didn't exactly seem like you were in the mood.
我現在也不太有心情
Oh, I'm not in the mood right now either.
我要去外面透透氣
I am gonna go outside and get some air.
你為何不待在這里想想
Why don't you just stay here and figure out
還能不能犯點別的罪
if there's some other crime you can commit
來擺脫這件事
to get out of this one?
這件事一出問題你就應該打電話給我的
You should have called me the minute this went down.
當時沒時間了
There wasn't time.
你可有時間去見艾莉森·霍特啊
You had time to see Allison Holt.
我是想搶先解決這個問題
I was trying to get out in front of it.
艾莉森·霍特不是我們的問題
Allison Holt isn't our problem.
邁克·羅斯才是
Mike Ross is.
聯邦檢察官一直在到處窺探
The U.S. Attorney keeps poking around,
他會發現他的明星證人
he's gonna find out that his star witness
甚至都不是律師協會的
isn't even in the bar.
不  他不會發現的
No, he won't.
假如他們查看律師協會的記錄  會發現邁克·羅斯
If they look in the bar, they'll find Mike Ross
正是其中一員
listed as a member.
你讓他犯下了另一個重罪嗎
You had him commit another felony?
你想讓我大聲承認嗎
You want me to say that out loud?
不  我不想
No, I don't.
我比較想討論我們手頭的問題
I'd rather get back to the matter at hand.
我們要確保哈羅德·甘德森不會開口
We need to make sure Harold Gunderson doesn't talk.
那你就得多了解了解
Then you need to learn more
那個想撬開他的嘴的人
about the man who's trying to make him talk,
因為他是沖著你來的
because he's coming for you,
但你卻不知道他是誰
and you don't know who he is,
他會怎么做  他掌握了些什么
what he'll do, or what he's got.
我只知道一件事
I know one thing--
如果他有任何證據
if he had any kind of proof,
肯定有人已經被捕了
someone here would have already been arrested.
被捕  理由是什么
Arrested? For what?
我們正因為海辛頓案里和布萊頓·古爾德
We're being investigated for the settlement
達成的和解協議接受調查
between us and Bratton Gould in the Hessington case.
柯靈還沒放手嗎
Quelling didn't go away?
柯靈威脅說要去律師協會舉報我們
Quelling threatened to go to the bar.
但現在是聯邦檢察官辦公室在查
This is the U.S. Attorney's office.
除非指控有理有據  不然都不必擔心
Well, that only matters if the allegations have merit.
我從沒想過會這么問
I never thought I would have to ask this,
但指控是有理有據的嗎
but do the allegations have merit?
我們正在處理  斯科特
We're handling this, Scottie.
我沒問是誰在處理
I didn't ask who was handling it.
我問的是有沒有證據
I asked if they have merit.
斯科特  斯科特
Scottie. Scottie.
怎么  又要施展魅力了嗎
What, are you gonna be charming?
又要引用電視劇臺詞嗎
Quote a TV show?
不是說"我會做得更好"嗎
What happened to "I'm going to do better"?
該死的  我正努力著呢
God damn it, I'm trying.
哈維  我覺得你不知道努力是什么意思
Harvey, I don't think you understand what trying means.
這么說吧  斯科特  你總是覺得
You know what, scottie? You keep on thinking
有些事你被瞞在鼓里  但
that there are things being withheld from you, but--
但什么  只是公事嗎
But what? It's just business?
-確實只是公事  -好
- It is just business. - Fine.
作為高級合伙人  我想知道
As a senior partner, I want to know
這家律所是否公然違法
if this firm outright broke any laws.
-哈維  我得跟你談談  -現在不行  唐娜
- Harvey, I need to talk to you. - Not now, Donna.
如果你要讓我找斯特芬妮
If you want me to talk to Stephanie,
就得告訴我你要我問她些什么
you have to tell me what you want me to ask her right now.
我猜你會說"現在不是時候  斯科特"
I guess it's "Not now, Scottie."
邁克  邁克  我得跟你談談
Mike? Mike. I need to talk to you.
不  不  我現在甚至不能跟你待在一起
No, no, I can't even be seen with you.
-快走  -但你必須得跟我談談
- Go, now. - But you have to talk to me.
艾莉森·霍特剛剛無緣無故解雇了我
Allison Holt just fired me out of the blue.
-我現在怕得要死  伙計  -哈羅德  聽我說
- I'm freaking out, man. - Harold, listen to me.
冷靜下來  行不
You have to calm down, all right?
哈羅德·甘德森  這里不歡迎你
Harold Gunderson, you're not welcome here.
別打岔  路易
You know what, Louis?
我們正聊著事情呢  所以
We're kind of in the middle of something right now, so--
我不管  邁克  幫個忙
Well, I don't give a shit. Mike, do me a favor.
別讓這個不識抬舉的前員工進入我們的辦公室
Do not let this unappreciative ex-employee into our offices.
哈羅德  你得走了  現在就走
Harold, you have to go, right now.
不  等等  邁克  拜托了
No, wait, mike. Please.
聯邦檢察官辦公室給我打了電話
I got a call from the U.S. Attorney's office
要我去一趟
asking for me to come in.
不知道為什么  他們盯上了我們干的事
Somehow, they're onto what we did,
-我覺得我們得  -哈羅德  哈羅德
- and I think we need to-- - Harold, Harold, Harold. Harold.
我只知道是你堅持要簽和解協議
All I know about that settlement is that you stuck it to us
因為你覺得這是個報復我們解雇你的好機會
because you saw the chance to get back at us for firing you.
-邁克  不是這樣  -我不想聽  哈羅德
- Mike, that's not true. - I don't want to hear it, Harold.
你的行為是打擊報復
What you did was harsh and vindictive,
但卻完全合法  因為是你提出的
but it was completely legal because you initiated it.
人人影視
YYeTs.com
只要我們都記著這一點  沒人能
And nobody can prove anything other than that
拿出什么別的證據
as long as we both remember it.
-我丟了工作  邁克  -很遺憾  哈羅德
- I lost my job, Mike. - I'm sorry about that, Harold.
我希望能幫你點什么
I wish there was something I could do.
但現在我得回去了
Now I have to go back inside.
邁克·羅斯  哈羅德·甘德森
Michael Ross, Harold Gunderson,
你們被捕了
You're under arrest
罪名是共謀欺詐美國政府
for conspiracy to defraud the United States Government.
謝謝你來見我
Thanks for meeting with me.
唐娜  隨你怎么謝我
Donna, you can thank me all you want.
我一點都不知道埃里克·伍德爾的情況
I don't know anything about Eric Woodall.
斯特芬尼  別這樣
Stephanie, come on.
你對那間辦公室的舉動一清二楚
You know everything that goes on in that office.
只是不想告訴我
You just don't want to tell me.
你想知道什么
What do you want to know?
不如從他為什么沖著哈維來說起
Well, how about we start with why he's coming after Harvey?
因為他憎恨手腳不干凈的律師
Because he hates Dirty Lawyers.
認為他們是地球上的糟粕
He thinks they're the scum of the earth.
而哈維引起了他的注意
And Harvey got on his radar?
伍德爾之所以沒引起你們的注意
And the reason Woodall's not on your radar
是因為他花了四年打贏上一場官司
is because the last case he won took him four years.
你是說他絕不停手嗎
So you're saying he'll stop at nothing?
我從來沒見過
Not that I've ever seen.
那我們得搞清楚他手上有些什么
Then we need to know what he's got.
不行的
No way.
他們把你們的人帶進來時  我聯系了你
I called you when they brought your guy in.
就憑這一點我就可能會丟了工作
I could lose my job for that as it is.
你還有比工作重要得多的東西
You have something else a lot more important than your job,
都得感謝我
thanks to me.
你什么時候才能不拿這點來要挾我
When are you gonna stop holding that over my head?
如果你告訴我我想要的信息  我以后就不會要挾你了
In another 30 seconds if you tell me what I need to know.
好吧
Okay.
他沒有證據
He's got nothing.
但問題是  他沒證據也能贏
But the thing is, he wins with nothing.
你之前說  他憎恨手腳不干凈的律師
You just said he hates dirty lawyers,
現在你又說  他會違法辦事
and now you're saying he'll break the law?
有可能  也可能不違法
He may, he may not.
但他絕對能攪出事來
But he'll definitely bend the shit out of it.
我想知道是怎么回事
I want to know what's going on.
我告訴過你怎么回事
I told you what's going on.
哈維和我正在解決這個問題
Harvey and I are taking care of a situation.
這不算什么狗屁答案  你知道的
That's a bullshit answer, and you know it.
我不知道你和愛德華·達比是怎么相處的
I don't know how it went with you and Edward Darby,
但你帶著這樣的態度走進我的辦公室
but you come into my office with that attitude,
我可不會給你什么好果子吃
and it won't go well for you with me.
我這個態度是因為我給愛德華·達比干活
My attitude comes from the fact that I worked for Edward Darby.
-我可不想給另一個干  -你太過分了
- I don't want to work for another one. - You're way out of line.
你的名字不在這兒的門上
Your name is not on the door here.
是不在  但如果因為你和哈維做過的事
No, but if this all comes down because of something
律所聲名掃地  那我也會受到牽連
you and Harvey did, I'm tainted by it.
那就走人  斯科特  我不攔你
Then walk away, Scottie. I'm not stopping you.
你讓我簽署的不競爭條款攔著我呢
No, the noncompete you had me sign is stopping me.
是它在攔著你嗎
Is that what's stopping you?
杰西卡  我把我的生活搬回了紐約
Jessica, I moved my life back to New York.
我不想再搬走了
I don't want to move again.
我最后問你一次
So I'm asking you one more time--
到底怎么回事
what is going on?
具體怎么回事
What's going on...
就是你和哈維一時沖動決定讓你來這兒
is you and Harvey made an impulsive deal for you to come here,
顯然事情沒有你們預想的那么順
and clearly, it's not working out,
否則現在跟你說話的就不是我
or you'd be having this conversation with him
而是他了
and not me.
看看把誰帶來了
Well, look what the cat dragged in.
我已經在這里待了兩個小時
I've been in here for two hours.
你說我被捕了
You said I was under arrest,
但還沒人來審訊我
but I still haven't been processed.
我要求傳訊哈維
I demand to call Harvey.
抱歉  辦不到
Sorry, we can't have that.
那我猜你也不能判我或其他人有罪
Then I guess you can't have a guilty verdict against me or anybody else,
我知道我的權利
because I know my rights.
恐怕你的權利正好撞上了
Well, I'm afraid your rights have run smack into
一個叫《愛國者法案》的玩意兒
a little something called the Patriot Act.
不管你扯什么淡  都只適用于恐怖分子
Whatever bullshit you're trying to pull only applies to terrorists.
那我還碰上好事了
Then it's a good thing
海辛頓的證人還真指控了恐怖主義
there are allegations of terrorism against those Hessington witnesses.
你不會得逞的
You're not gonna get away with this.
我不得任何逞
I'm not getting away with anything.
只是通過調查這些指控  做到萬無一失
I'm just being thorough by looking into these allegations.
耐心點吧
Try to be patient.
也許  可以想想
Maybe, uh, think about the fact
哈羅德·甘德森在隔壁也努力耐著性子呢
that Harold Gunderson is trying to be patient right next door.
在踱步啊  不出我所料
Pacing. Right on schedule.
失敗的第一個征兆
First sign that a man is losing it.
這叫走路
It's called walking.
隨你怎么叫
You can call it what you want.
-我眼見為實  -是啊  我也是
- I know what I'm looking at. - Yeah. So do I.
調查了恐怖分子指控
A guy who looked into those terrorist allegations
卻毫無結論
and came up with nothing.
我得說關于那些證人的傳言毫無根據
I'll admit the rumors about those witnesses were unsubstantiated.
但如果我不調查一個和那些可疑的人
But I'd be negligent if I didn't look into an American
聯系緊密的美國人  那我就太大意了
with ties to such questionable characters.
你也永遠不會知道詳盡的背景調查
And you never know what a thorough background check
會發現些什么
is gonna turn up.
那請便吧
Then go ahead.
快去做背景調查  好讓我早點出去
Do your background check, so I can get out of here,
因為所有這些事搞得我好無聊
because all this is doing is making me bored.
這件事就交給我吧
Well, I can take care of that for you.
我把電視打開給你看看吧
Why don't I let you watch a little TV?
這才是踱步
Now, that's pacing.
發現任何關于埃里克·伍德爾的有用信息了嗎
Did you find out anything useful on Eric Woodall?
我發現我們該開始進攻了
I found out we need to start going on offense.
怎么進攻
How?
唐娜正在讓邁克整理所有
Donna's having Mike compile every piece of communication
人人影視
YYeTs.com
達成和解期間的通訊記錄
during that settlement to prove
證明是哈羅德先聯系我們的  而不是相反
Harold contacted us first, not the other way around.
-那是真實情況嗎  -你真的想知道嗎
- Is that true? - You really want to know?
那之后  我們需要審閱
After that, we're gonna read up on
伍德爾上一個案子所有的策略
every tactic Woodall used in his last case.
什么案子
Case?
花了他四年
Took him four years.
他還真是執著啊
Dog with a bone.
這就是我們要開始進攻的原因
That's why we're going on offense.
我也發現了一些事
Well, I found out something too.
斯科特想走了
Scottie wants to leave.
什么
What?
她想免除不競爭條款
She asked out of her noncompete.
你怎么答復她的
And what did you say?
我說我要和我的合伙人討論一下
I said I had to discuss it with my partner.
如果她要是能和她的另一半討論一下就好了
It would have been nice if she discussed it with her partner.
她指責我做了一些很壞的勾當
She accused me of some pretty shady shit.
而且她沒說錯
And she's right.
你指什么
What are you talking about?
我告訴過你
I told you earlier,
我并不想知道邁克和他從業資格的事
I didn't want to know about Mike and the bar,
就在剛才  你還問我是否想知道
and just now, you asked me if I wanted to know
邁克和哈羅德的事
about Mike and Harold, and again,
我還是不想知道
I didn't want to know.
而愛德華·達比也是這么說的
And "I don't want to know" is exactly what Edward Darby said.
我們不是他
We're not him.
愛德華·達比并沒有犯下那些謀殺案
Edward Darby didn't commit those murders.
他只是掩蓋了它們
He just covered them up.
在我看來  我們也在不停的做一些事
And it seems to me we keep doing things,
然后再不得不把它們掩蓋起來
and then we have to keep covering them up.
我們不是他
We're not him.
哈維
Harvey.
你想讓我怎么答復斯科特
What do you want me to tell Scottie?
如果她不想在這待下去了
If she doesn't want to be here,
就讓她走吧
let her go.
你都做了些什么
What the hell did you do?
你知道我做了什么
You know what I did.
我向協會舉報了你
I handed you in to the bar.
邁克·羅斯和我達成了協議
Mike Ross and I had a deal.
從他被聯邦檢察官帶去問話的那一刻起
Yeah, well, that deal went away when he got brought in
那個協議就作廢了
for questioning by the U.S. Attorney.
什么  那不是我干的
What? That wasn't me.
我沒有找過他們
I didn't go to them.
我不在乎你有沒有找過他們
I don't give a shit if you went to them or not.
這整件事都是因為你被賄賂
This whole thing started when you walked into my office
而要起訴我們開始的
with a lawsuit you were bribed to create.
但在那之后  我和邁克達成了協議
And after that, I made a deal with Mike.
我也信守了我的承諾
And I held to my end of the bargain.
也許你剛才沒聽清
Maybe you didn't hear me.
他們把他帶走  關起來
That deal went away when they picked him up,
并讓他試圖把我供出來時
hauled him in, and then tried to get him
協議就作廢了
to turn on me.
你還有能力阻止這一切
Well, you can still stop this.
但我不打算那么做
Yeah, well, I'm not going to.
那你最好在余生的
Well, then you better look over your shoulder every day
每一天都提高警惕了
for the rest of your natural-born life.
-你說什么  -你知道我說什么
- What did you say? - You heard me.
聽我說  你這個混蛋
Listen to me, you son of a bitch.
你掏出支槍  威脅要殺我的人
You pulled out a gun and threatened to shoot my guy,
我不在乎你的本意是什么
and I don't give a shit if you didn't mean to shoot it,
最終槍響了
because it went off.
他們就是因為你才會調查我
They're looking into me because of you.
如果我再聽到你的名字
And I ever so much as hear your name again,
我會找到你  讓你粉身碎骨
I will find you, and I will break every bone in your body.
你就是個傲慢的混蛋
You are nothing but a badass on his high horse.
混蛋先生  也許確實是我導致
Well, Mr. Badass, I may have started them
他們開始調查你的
looking into what you did,
但事情都是你自己做的
but you were the one who did it.
柯靈  趕緊走吧你
Quelling, be on your way.
瑞秋  你看到邁克了嗎
Rachel, have you seen Mike?
路易  我沒有
No, Louis, I haven't.
好吧  出什么事了嗎
Okay. Is something wrong?
是有點事  我們吵架了
Yeah, something's wrong. We got into a fight.
之后就再沒見過他了
I haven't seen him since.
自從他和哈羅德談過以后我就沒見過他了
Well, I haven't seen him since he was talking to Harold,
-但我需要他給  -他和哈羅德談過
- but I need him to give me-- - He was talking to harold?
是啊  我也不清楚
Yeah, I don't know, they were having
他們在樓外傻兮兮的吵  怎么了
some idiotic fight outside. Why?
沒什么  我必須和哈維談談
No, it's nothing. I have to go talk to harvey.
等一下  哈維
Whoa, wait a second. Harvey?
這件事和他今早
Does this have something to do
沒來開會有關系嗎
with why he missed his meeting this morning?
我不能說
I can't.
瑞秋
Rachel.
你必須告訴我到底出了什么事
You need to tell me what the hell's going on right now.
唐娜  我知道你看到了大廳里的事
Donna, I know you saw what happened in the lobby.
我不想聽你提這件事
I don't want to hear about it.
哈維  我找不到邁克了
Harvey, I can't find Mike.
什么
What?
我試過郵件  信息
I've tried his email, I've tried texting,
所有地方都找了
I've looked everywhere.
我要說的是  邁克失蹤了
I'm telling you, Mike is nowhere to be found.
-路易  等一下  -不能等  哈維
- Louis, not now. - Yes, now, Harvey.
我知道他在哪
I know where he is.
他和哈羅德·甘德森一起被捕了
He's under arrest, along with Harold Gunderson.
我們必須馬上趕過去
We need to get down there right now.
讓我理一理
Let me get this straight.
我們逮捕你們的時候
You two were in a heated conversation
你們兩個正在進行很激烈的討論
when we picked you up,
但內容與這件事無關
and that had nothing to do with this.
方方面面都有關
It had everything to do with it.
你是說你正試圖掩蓋罪行嗎
You mean you were trying to cover your tracks.
不  我們在激烈的討論
No, we were having a heated conversation
這些指控是多么的無稽
about what bullshit charges these are.
我受夠了跟你玩游戲了
Okay, I'm done playing your games.
他是你在那個律所唯一的朋友  你被開除了
He was your only friend at that firm, you got fired.
你給他找了另一份工作
You got him another job,
因此你就去找他策劃了這整件事
and that's why you went to him to set this whole thing up.
你的消息都是錯的
You've got your information wrong.
他不是我的朋友
He wasn't my friend.
我有機會挽回他的工作
I had the chance to save his job...
但他卻把我拋下不管了
But instead, he threw me under the bus.
所以我才會發起這個訴訟
That is why I instituted this lawsuit.
所以你可以帶著你的指控滾了
So you can take your bullshit allegations somewhere else
我不會為此犧牲哈維的
because I am not gonna roll on Harvey.
我不會犧牲邁克的
I'm not rolling on mike.
哈羅德也不會犧牲我的
And Harold is not gonna roll on me.
你們排練的不錯啊
You guys are well rehearsed.
所以我要再問一次
So I'll ask you again,
今天你們在街上就是在做這件事嗎
is that what you were doing on the street today?
老天爺啊  你開車慢的跟我外婆一樣
Jesus Christ, you know, you drive like my nana--
他開的像我外婆  她102歲了
He drives like my nana, and she's 102.
放松點  路易  雷盡力了
Relax, Louis. Ray's on it.
沒人能讓我們更快到那了
Nobody's getting us there faster.
我簡直不敢相信發生了這件事
I mean, I can't believe this whole thing's been going on
而且我完全被蒙在鼓里
and I've been completely out of the loop.
路易  我不想多說什么了
Louis, I don't want to rehash it.
當務之急  邁克被關起來了
Right now, Mike's in custody.
我們得把他救出來
We need to get him out.
你得告訴我這到底是怎么回事
Yeah, and you need to tell me what the hell happened.
你是在問我們和哈羅德
Are you asking if we broke the law
和解的時候是否違法了嗎
when we made that settlement with Harold?
我就是想問這個
That's exactly what I'm asking.
確實有點問題
We have exposure.
人人影視
YYeTs.com
那你最好祈禱雷開快點
Well, then you better hope that Ray drives
因為你我都明白
a little goddamn faster, because you and I both know
那里正發生什么事
what's going on in there.
我來跟你說說現在的處境吧
Let me tell you what we are dealing with here.
密謀賄賂證人  七年
Conspiring to bribe witnesses-- seven years.
你為了支持自己的案件遞交了宣誓說明
You filed a sworn declaration in support of your suit.
這是偽證罪  再加兩年
That's perjury-- another two years.
除此之外
And to top it all off,
錢是從境外轉來的
the money was transferred overseas,
所以這是...
which would be--
你也是律師  你自己說
Well, you're a lawyer. Fill in the blank.
-匯款詐騙  -答對了
- Wire fraud. - Bingo.
你中大獎了  獎品是再加二十年
Big winner. And your prize is 20 more years.
丑話說在前面  我保證你要去的
And here's the thing. I am gonna make sure
絕不會是輕松安逸的白領監獄
that it's not a cushy white-collar prison.
太荒唐了
This is just ridiculous.
如果哈羅德現在還能撐住  我真要嚇尿了
If Harold isn't broken by now, I'll shit my pants.
如果哈羅德撐不住了  那等我們到那兒
If Harold's broken, then when we get there,
邁克就要去坐牢了
Mike's gonna be on his way to prison.
他需要有人幫他一把
Someone needs to get in there and hold his hand.
不是隨便什么人都行
Not someone...
-只能是你  -你說真的嗎
- You. - Are you serious?
哈羅德·甘德森現在
I'm the last person in the world
最不想見到的人就是我了
that Harold Gunderson wants to see right now.
路易  我們還是助理律師的時候
Louis, when we were associates,
你最怕的是誰
who did you fear most?
當然是我媽
That's easy. My mother.
我是說在律所里
I meant in the firm.
丹尼爾·哈德曼
Daniel Hardman.
所以如果換了是你在那個房間
So who would you most want to come in
你會希望是誰走進來
and take on Eric Woodall,
收拾埃里克·伍德爾
if you were in that room?
-丹尼爾·哈德曼  -這就對了
- Daniel Hardman. - Exactly.
聽著  哈羅德或許不喜歡你
Look, Harold may not like you,
但他尊重你  而他現在是孤身作戰
but he respects you, and he's all alone.
等我們到了那兒
Now, when we get there,
我希望你激發出你內心的哈德曼
I need you to channel your inner Hardman,
得到他的信任
get him to trust you,
然后讓他給我閉嘴
and then shut him the hell up.
我能跟你談談嗎
Can I talk to you for a second?
你好像憂心忡忡的
You look concerned.
你知道為什么當初哈維要雇一個
Do you know why I never batted an eye when I found out
沒上過法學院的小屁孩時  我眼都沒眨一下嗎
Harvey had hired a kid who didn't go to law school?
因為你對他忠心耿耿
Because you're loyal to him.
因為我知道他內心所想
Because I knew what was inside him.
我覺得如果他有個徒弟
And I thought if he had a protege--
他完全可以從哈佛找個徒弟
He could have hired a protege from Harvard.
那他就不會被逼著去保護他了
But he wouldn't have been forced to protect him.
他也不會成為如今的他
And he wouldn't have become the man he is today.
現在他的徒弟有麻煩了
Well, now that protege is in trouble.
他們拘留了邁克和哈羅德·甘德森
They have Mike and Harold Gunderson in custody.
那哈維也有麻煩了
Then harvey's in trouble too.
不
No.
邁克絕不會背叛哈維的
Mike would never turn on Harvey.
你根本不知道在那個房間里
You never know what might happen to a person
會發生些什么
once they get in that room.
他現在沒空  斯科特
Not now, Scottie.
唐娜  我只是留個言告訴他我想談談
Donna, I'm just writing him a note telling him I wanted to talk.
談談
"To talk."
我想你根本不知道他有多努力
I don't think you know how hard he's trying.
我知道他在努力
I know he's trying.
但我不確定是否這樣就夠了
I'm just not sure that it's good enough.
你早就知道他是什么樣的人  斯科特
You knew who he was, Scottie.
可我以為他會改變
And I thought he would change.
我覺得他已經變了  如果你還是覺得不夠
I think he has changed, and if it's not enough for you, then--
這不是問題所在
That's not the problem.
我是覺得他變得太多了
I think that he's changed too much,
而且是在我回來之前就變了
and I think it happened before I got back.
他是個好人  斯科特
He's a good man, Scottie,
但人無完人
but he's not perfect.
有時候  你只能選擇安于現狀
Sometimes you just have to take what you get,
或斬斷情絲
or walk away.
知道嗎  幾年前他們做過一個試驗
You know, they did an experiment a few years back.
把五只老鼠關在籠子里
Took five mice, put 'em in a cage,
喂食的量只夠他們勉強生存  你猜發生了什么
fed them just enough to survive, and you know what happened?
它們接連將最弱的老鼠逼至角落
One by one, they cornered the weakest mouse
生吞活吃了
and ate him alive.
你知道你進監獄后會怎樣嗎  邁克
You know what you're gonna be when you get to prison, Mike?
-你就是那最弱的老鼠  -扯淡
- The weakest mouse. - Bullshit.
他們是做過研究  我看過報告
They have done studies, and I've read them,
根本不是你說的那樣
and that's not what happens.
老鼠只有在被別的種族洗腦之后
The only way a mouse eats one of his own
才會蠶食自己的種族
is if he's been contaminated by another species.
你說得對  我確實是扯淡的
Yeah, you're right. It's bullshit.
不過你猜猜是誰在五分鐘前
But you know who believed it when I told it to him,
信了我的扯淡呢
five minutes ago?
哈羅德
Harold.
看來你的時間到了  哈羅德打算開口了
Looks like you're out of time. Harold's ready to talk.
你有沒有什么想先說的
You want to tell me something first?
在他改變主意之前趕緊去見他
Get to him before he changes his mind.
-我要求見我的當事人  -你可以見
- I demand to see my client. - You can see him,
但我不會放了他  因為五分鐘后
but I'm not letting him go, 'cause in five minutes,
我就會回來給他致命一擊
I'm gonna come back to him with a sledgehammer.
別急
Not so fast.
我要求見我的當事人
I demand to see my client,
我當事人不是邁克·羅斯  是哈羅德·甘德森
and my client isn't Mike Ross, it's Harold Gunderson.
-你是  -路易·利特  皮爾遜-斯佩克特的
- And you are? - Louis Litt, Pearson Specter.
人人影視
YYeTs.com
你是說他現在被控與之合謀的
You're telling me that a man who works at the law firm
那個律所的雇員恰好就是他的律師
he's accused of colluding with just happens to be his attorney?
正是如此
That's exactly what I'm saying.
-你扯淡  -我沒有
- Bullshit. - No.
扯淡的是你居然以為哈羅德·甘德森
What's bullshit is you thinking it's up to you
選誰做代理律師是由你說了算的
who gets to represent Harold Gunderson.
所以如果我走進那個房間
So if I walk in there right now
問他誰是他的律師  他會說是你嗎
and ask him who his attorney is, he's gonna say it's you?
他說什么不重要
Doesn't matter what he says.
根據第407條法規  如果你不讓我見我的當事人
It's 407, and if you don't let me see my client,
此刻開始他說的所有話都不可采納為證詞
anything he says after this second will be inadmissible.
而我會用第四修正案
And I will rain down fourth amendment claims on you
第四修正案禁止不合理的搜查和抓捕
追著你告一輩子
for the rest of your goddamn life.
如果你想自己休息一會  只管開口
If you wanted some me time, all you had to do was ask.
你最好告訴我點好消息
You'd better have some good news for me,
不然我就要休息很久了
otherwise I'm gonna be having plenty of me time.
哈維  這個叫伍德爾的家伙是來真的
Harvey, this Woodall guy is serious.
-我也是來真的  -那我為什么還呆在這兒
- I'm serious too. - Then why am I still in here?
因為我們在等路易
Because we're waiting for Louis.
路易  他要干什么
Louis? To do what?
說服哈羅德別開口
Convince Harold not to talk.
我了個去  路易和哈羅德在一起
Holy shit. Louis is in with Harold?
哈羅德討厭路易
Harold hates Louis!
這是最好的辦法了
It's our best shot.
那我們現在干什么
So what do we do now?
等著
We wait.
路易  你來干什么
Louis, what are you doing here?
首先  你怎么樣了
First off, how you doing?
你覺得我怎么樣了
How do you think I'm doing?
我已經下到地獄第七層了
I'm in the seventh circle of hell.
騎士來拯救你了
Well, the cavalry has arrived.
我不需要騎士  我要出去
I don't need the cavalry. I've decided to get out.
哈羅德   你不能簽協議
Okay, Harold, you cannot sign a deal.
簽了你就再也不能當律師了
You'll never work as a lawyer again.
你在乎嗎  我當律師的時候是你炒了我
What do you care? You fired me as a lawyer.
現在你有求于我
Now all of a sudden you're my best friend
就突然變成我的摯友了  見鬼去吧  路易
when you need something from me? Go to hell, Louis!
知道嗎
Okay, you know what?
你說得對
You're right.
我不是你的朋友  從來不是
I'm not your friend. Never was.
但我從未欺騙過你
But the one thing I've never done is lie to you.
你現在有機會毫發無傷地走出這道門
Now, you have a chance to walk out of here today,
好像什么事都沒發生過一樣
as if none of this has ever happened,
只要你相信我
and all you have to do is trust me.
你根本不明白他是怎樣的人
You have no idea who that man is.
不明白
No idea?
那你以為我怎么進來的
How do you think I got in the room?
好吧  路易
Okay, well, you know, Louis,
很高興你能認真對待這件事
I am glad you got to take a good look at it,
因為如果我不供出邁克
because if I don't give them Mike,
我就要在這呆一輩子了
I could be in here for the rest of my life.
律師光看著窗外是領不到工資的
Lawyers don't get paid to look out the window.
我也無法集中注意力
I can't concentrate either.
我只是希望能盡一份力
I just wish there was something we could do.
瑞秋  如果這個案子上了法庭
Rachel, if this thing moves forward to trial,
我會不遺余力去贏
I will do everything in my power to win.
但離比賽結束只有兩分鐘了
But there's two minutes left in the game,
而我們最好的隊員都在場上
and our star players are on the field.
所以現在  我們只能選擇相信他們
So right now, we just have to have faith.
我們
W-we?
We.
你會在這里工作
You're going to work here.
我們會成為一家人
We're going to be family.
而了解家人的最好辦法就是當他們愛的人
And the way to get to know your family is by being with them
遇到麻煩時陪在他們身邊
when their loved ones are in trouble.
我們要等多久
How long do we wait?
等到一切結束
As long as it takes.
我想跟你談談我的辯護策略
I want to talk to you about my defense strategy.
這就是你的辯護策略
This is your defense strategy.
如果不管用
If this doesn't work,
你就去找別的律師談吧
you're gonna want to talk to a different lawyer than me.
哈維  我不管哈羅德跟他們說了什么
Harvey, I don't care what Harold gives them on me,
我不會出賣你的
I'm not giving them you.
-我想跟你講個故事  -我不想聽故事
- I want to tell you a story. - I don't want to hear a story.
是關于我跟我爸說我媽的事
It's about the time I decided to tell my dad about my mom.
你還記得我跟你說過些什么嗎
You remember what I told you about her?
-哈維  -我當時20歲
- Harvey-- - I was 20,
離家在外
out of the house,
我跟我媽說只要她別帶人回家
and I told her I would never tell him
我就不會告訴我爸
as long as she never brought anyone--
有一天我回家洗衣服  然后我聽到了
I came home to do laundry one day, and I heard--
我聽到了
I heard,
然后我還看到了  那天晚上我就跟我爸說了
and then I saw, and I told him that night.
因為有時候說出來會更好
Because sometimes it's better to tell.
她那是活該
She deserved that.
我也是
So do I.
這一切都是我的主意
This whole thing was my idea.
是我做的決定  伍德爾的目標是我
I gave the go-ahead. It's me Woodall wants.
-他的目標不是你  -不  就是我
- Well, he's not getting you! - Yes, he is.
不  不管那間屋子里發生了什么
No, I don't care what happens in that room,
我不會放棄你的
I'm not giving you up!
-別傻了  -別混了
- Don't be a fool. - Don't be an asshole!
聽我說  該死的  我允許你
Listen to me, God damn it, I'm giving you permission--
我才不管你要給我什么
I don't give a shit what you're giving me!
我雇了個騙子
I hired a fraud.
我們在克利福德·丹納案上越過了底線
And then we crossed the line with Clifford Danner,
然后是羅拉·詹森  之后是那些目擊者
then with Lola Jensen, and then with these witnesses,
到最后
and to top it all off,
愛德華·達比的案子我們還唆使作偽證
we suborned perjury with Edward Darby.
真到這一關頭  你就把責任都推給我  明白嗎
If it comes to it, you point the finger at me, you got that?
我們就祈禱不會到這關頭吧
Let's just hope it doesn't come to it.
結束了  我們出去吧
It's over. Let's get the hell out of here.
邁克  怎么樣
Hey, Mike. How's it going?
人人影視
YYeTs.com
斯佩克特先生
Mr. Specter!
埃里克
Eric.
你阻止了岡德森作證
Just because you stopped Gunderson from testifying
并不意味著我就會撤銷這案子
doesn't mean I'm dropping this case.
那就別撤銷
Then don't.
我要告你們惡意指控
And I'll come after you for malicious prosecution.
你沒有根據
You have no basis for that.
你們逮捕了我的當事人  他已經在這里待了4小時
You arrested my client, he was here four hours,
沒有任何記錄顯示你們聯系過我
and you have no log with an outgoing call to me,
完全根據捏造的恐怖主義指控
All on the basis of a fabricated terrorism claim.
如果這還不是惡意  那什么才是
Now, if that's not malicious, I don't know what is.
你隨便怎么說
You say what you want.
你這個無良律師  我會時刻盯著你的
You're a dirty lawyer, and now you're on my radar.
如果我是個無良律師
If I'm a dirty lawyer,
那你就是在照鏡子
then you're looking in the mirror.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我還以為我再也
I just thought that I would never--
都沒事了
Everything's gonna be okay.
親愛的  我到家了
Hey, honey, I'm home.
你有記得按我說的去接孩子嗎
Did you remember to pick up the kids like I asked?
記得啊
Yep.
最小的那個還真是棘手得很
The youngest one's turning into a real pain in the ass.
-你能回來真好  -回來真好
- It's good to have you back. - Good to be back.
你在想什么  哈維
What's on your mind, Harvey?
你說得對  我們正在變成愛德華
You were right. We are becoming Edward.
我知道
I know.
我們得變回我們本來的樣子
And we need to get back to being us.
你告訴她我們的決定了嗎
Did you let her know about our decision yet?
我以為你想親自去說
I assumed you'd want to take care of that yourself.
你想來一杯嗎
You want a drink?
《廣告狂人》上就是這么做的  對嗎
They do it on Mad Men, right?
杰西卡和我決定免除你的不競爭條款
Jessica and I are gonna let you out of your noncompete.
那入股金怎么辦
What about the buy-in?
入股金我們來處理
We'll take care of the buy-in.
哈維  我
Harvey, I, um--
邁克·羅斯從沒上過法學院
Mike Ross never went to law school.
我知道  但我還是雇了他
I knew it, and I hired him anyway.
你為什么現在要告訴我
Why are you telling me now?
因為你指責杰西卡正在變成愛德華·達比
Because you accused Jessica of being Edward Darby.
不是她  是我
It wasn't her. It was me.
我還是不能留下來  哈維
I still can't stay, Harvey.
我知道
I know.
我只是不想再欺騙我愛的人了
I just want to stop lying to the people I love.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我告訴她了
I told her.
我知道
I know.
-她不會告訴任何人的  -我知道
- She won't tell anyone. - I know.
她要走了
She's leaving.
我知道
I know.
人人影視
YYeTs.com
哈維  你是個好人
Harvey, you're a good man.
是嗎
Am I?
我向律師協會舉報了柯靈
I turned Quelling into the bar.
我拿他出了氣
I took my rage out on him.
不該由他受這些氣
He didn't deserve it.
所以我撤銷了
Which is why I stopped it.
你在說什么呢
What are you talking about?
你難道真以為欠我人情的
Do you seriously think that Stephanie Liston
只有斯特芬尼·利斯頓一人嗎
is the only person who owes me a favor?
那也不會把我變成好人
Well, that doesn't make me a good man.
而是把你變成了好人
That makes you a good man for me.
哈維  有時候我們也需要一些幫助
Harvey, sometimes we need a little help.
今天真夠嗆
Big day.
也很恐怖
Horrible day.
但結局是好的
It ended well.
謝謝
Thank you.
你和路易真的成功了
You and Louis really came through.
你也是
So did you.
聽著  我知道你在想什么
Look, I know what you're thinking.
-不  你不知道  -你不想進監獄
- No, you don't. - You don't want to go to jail.
哈維
Harvey...
我今天坐在那屋子里  聽你說
I sat in that room today and listened to you tell me
從我們認識的那天起
that ever since the day we met,
你不得不越過一道
you've had to cross one line
-又一道底線  -邁克
- after another, and-- - Mike--
不  聽我說完
No, just... let me finish.
一開始是克利福德·丹納
First there was Clifford Danner,
然后是目擊證人
then the witnesses,
之后是唆使作偽證  更別提我們
then suborning perjury, not to mention the 17 things
為了阻止合并所做的17件事了
we did to stop the merger in the first place.
這一切  都是你雇我之后的事
All of it, since you hired me.
聽著  我不是那個意思
Look, that's not what I said.
就是這樣
Yes, it is.
我不是在怪你
I wasn't blaming you for those things.
沒關系
It doesn't matter.
我受夠了把我在乎的人置于危險境地
I'm tired of putting the people I care about in jeopardy.
我下午給喬納森·西德威爾打電話了
I called Jonathan Sidwell this afternoon.
我接受了那份工作
I took the job.
我們才剛剛渡過難關
We just got out.
哈維
Harvey...
你允許我把責任都推向你
you gave me permission to point the finger at you.
也允許我走吧
Give me permission to go.
你是個好人  哈維
You're a good man, Harvey.
謝謝
Thanks.
你什么時候走
Hey, when's your last day?
我不知道  怎么了
I don't know. Why?
我想帶你出去吃頓飯
Well, I want to take you out to dinner, you know?
我再也不會見你了
I'm not gonna see you anymore.
你還沒搞清楚  我不會真的離開
I don't think you realize, but I'm not exactly leaving.
西德威爾  是我們的客戶
Sidwell. You're a client.
就是說嚴格說來  你現在是為我工作
Which means technically, you work for me now.
不  我才不
No, I don't.
不  我才不  老板
"No, I don't, boss."
-別逗了  -或者"先生"
- Don't even try it. - Or "Sir."
哪個讓你不舒服就叫哪個
Whichever feels least comfortable.
既然我現在一個人工作
You know, since I'm working alone now,
那我就是超人了
I guess that makes me superman.
或者水行俠  既然你這么傻缺
Or Aquaman, seeing as you're in over your head.